so
Chef what makes you
think that I'm going to let the whitest man that I
have ever seen interview for our firm
because I have an appointment.
You can do this.
Kid, what is wrong with you? You look like
you're 11 years old. I was lead to
puberty.
Okay.
Excuse me. I was thinking about
going for a swim or the pool facilities here.
Nice.
Of course sir. It's the children Hotel
best in the city. What
is the pool clothes and killed the
time? Yes,
ten o'clock.
Thanks.
Saw your gun. You think that's him?
That's the description I didn't go in the room and
exactly is just walking by
stay on the radio.
Rick Sorkin
Rick Sorkin,
excuse me. Mr. Sorkin you are
five minutes late. Is there a reason why I should let
you in.
I'm just trying to ditch the cops. Okay. I don't really care if you
let me in or not.
Mr. Specter will be right with you.
What can I get you anything a coffee
or bottled water?
Hi Rick Sorkin. I respect her
nice to meet you. She have a seat here.
Whoa, what's this?
Can I help you?
No.
Excuse me. Mr. Tate. My name
is Louis Litt. I work for Pearson Hardman.
I have some information that I think will lead you to the
conclusion that you're better served in Pearson with me
as your lead counsel.
I'm listening.
How the hell did you know they were to the
police? I read this novel in
elementary school.
Cops are staking out a hotel one of them dresses as
a bellhop the others a man in a
suit and it was the exact same thing. You
read a novel, you know Elementary
School what I like to
read.
And why'd you ask them what time it was throw them
off? And what kind of drug dealer
asks a cop with time it is when he's got a
briefcase full of pot right? We
should hire you
Jesus. I'd give you the 25 Grand is a
signing bonus. I'll take it.
Unfortunately, we only hire from Harvard and you
not only did not go to Harvard Law
School.
You haven't even gone to any law school.
What if I told you that I consume knowledge like no
one you've ever met and I've actually passed the
bar. I'd say you're full of
crap.
That's a Barbie legal handbook right there,
right?
Open it up read me something anything.
Civil liability associated with agency is based
on several factors, including the
deviation of the agent from his path the
reasonable inference of agency on behalf of the
plaintiff and the nature of the
damages themselves.
How did you know that I learned it
when I studied for the bar?
Okay, how it shut?
first this laptop
I'm going to show you.
What a Harvard attorney can do
pick a topic.
Stock option backdating. Although backdating options is
legal violations. Arise
related to disclosures under
IRC section. 409a
you forgot about sarbanes-oxley statute of
limitations render. Sarbanes-oxley moot post
2007. Well not if you can
find actions to cover up the violation
as established in the sixth circuit May
2008.
It's impressive, but you're sitting at a computer.
playing hearts
Sorry, if you want to beat me you're gonna have to do it as something
else. How can you
know all that? I told you I like to
read and once I read something
I understand it and once I understand
it.
I never forget it when I take the bar.
This dickhead bet me I couldn't pass it without going to law school.
Okay, look this is all
pretty fascinating stuff, but I'm afraid I got to get back to work.
I'll make sure the Serpico isn't around waiting for you.
You want this job so much. Why don't you just go to law
school?
When I was in college, it was my dream to be a
lawyer. I needed some money
and Trevor convinced me to memorize
this math test and sell
it.
Turns out we sold it to the Dean's daughter. I
lost my scholarship. I got kicked out of
school.
I got knocked into a different life.
And I have been wishing for a way back ever since.
Let me tell you something. This is an
elementary school. This is hard work
long hours high pressure.
I need a grown goddamn man.
You give me this and I will work as hard as it takes
to school those Harvard douches and become the
best lawyer you have ever seen.
I'm inclined to give you a shot. But what if I decided to go another
way I say that's fair
and sometimes I like to hang out with people who aren't that
bright. It was just to see how the other half
lives.
Move over. I'm emailing The Firm. I
just found our next associate.